<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-01-21T16:53:48-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/feed.xml</id><title type="html">My awesome blog</title><subtitle>This is the description of the my awesome blog.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Code Syntax Highlights</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/2022/01/16/code-syntax-highlights.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Code Syntax Highlights" /><published>2022-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-01-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/2022/01/16/code-syntax-highlights</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/2022/01/16/code-syntax-highlights.html">&lt;p&gt;Test rendering a code block with syntax highlighting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;foo&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'foo'&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;author is: xx&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&quot;/jekylltest/authors/xx.html&quot;&gt;author&lt;/a&gt;’s page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;page author is: /authors/xx.html&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nature" /><category term="plant" /><category term="yellow" /><summary type="html">Test rendering a code block with syntax highlighting.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">JC Raulston Arboretum</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/nature/garden/2021/08/30/jc-raulston-arboretum.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="JC Raulston Arboretum" /><published>2021-08-30T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-08-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/nature/garden/2021/08/30/jc-raulston-arboretum</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/nature/garden/2021/08/30/jc-raulston-arboretum.html">&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://jcra.ncsu.edu//horticulture/gardens/&quot;&gt;NCSU&lt;/a&gt; 
Many exquisite gardens set the stage for displaying new plant introductions at the JC Raulston Arboretum. Many of these areas follow a formal design with a particular theme, while others address contemporary issues or display new techniques in landscape design. Some of the gardens were designed and built primarily by students in landscape horticulture classes. The gardens are maintained by volunteer leaders under the supervision of the JCRA staff. A stroll through the gardens in any season is a rich experience, each one inspiring new ideas that can be directly used in your home gardens and landscapes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inherent in the JCRA philosophy is change. When gardens have outlived their potential or become outdated, they are redesigned into new features. This dynamic nature of the gardens ensures opportunities to educate audiences on current trends and techniques in horticulture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See post about &lt;a href=&quot;/jekylltest/nature/garden/2021/07/29/duke-garden-visit.html&quot;&gt;Duke Garden&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nature" /><category term="garden" /><category term="nature" /><category term="garden" /><category term="flower" /><summary type="html">Source: NCSU Many exquisite gardens set the stage for displaying new plant introductions at the JC Raulston Arboretum. Many of these areas follow a formal design with a particular theme, while others address contemporary issues or display new techniques in landscape design. Some of the gardens were designed and built primarily by students in landscape horticulture classes. The gardens are maintained by volunteer leaders under the supervision of the JCRA staff. A stroll through the gardens in any season is a rich experience, each one inspiring new ideas that can be directly used in your home gardens and landscapes.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Duke Garden Visit</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/nature/garden/2021/07/29/duke-garden-visit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Duke Garden Visit" /><published>2021-07-29T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-07-29T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/nature/garden/2021/07/29/duke-garden-visit</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/nature/garden/2021/07/29/duke-garden-visit.html">&lt;p&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://gardens.duke.edu/about/history&quot;&gt;Duke University&lt;/a&gt;
Sarah P. Duke Gardens has been serving the Duke and Durham communities for more than 80 years. The idea of a public garden arose in the early 1930s, due to the vision and enthusiasm of Dr. Frederic M. Hanes, an early member of the original faculty of Duke Medical School.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Hanes deeply loved gardening and was determined to convert the debris-filled ravine, by which he walked daily, into a garden of his favorite flower, the iris. In the previous decade, the land had been under consideration for creation of a lake. But funds were short and that project was abandoned. So the idea for a garden took root.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Hanes persuaded his friend Sarah P. Duke, widow of one of the university’s founders, Benjamin N. Duke, to give $20,000 to finance a garden that would bear her name. You may read her letter of approval in the slideshow above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1935, more than 100 flower beds were in glorious bloom in the area that is now the South Lawn. They included 40,000 irises, 25,000 daffodils, 10,000 small bulbs, and assorted annuals. Alas, heavy summer rains and the flooding stream caused washouts and disease, including iris rot.
By the time Sarah P. Duke died in 1936, the original gardens were in decline. Dr. Hanes convinced her daughter, Mary Duke Biddle, to construct a new garden on higher ground, as a fitting memorial to her mother. Ellen Biddle Shipman (1869-1950), a pioneer in American landscape design, was selected to design the plans for both the construction and the plantings for the new gardens. Sarah P. Duke Gardens was dedicated in April 1939 (see archival footage from the dedication here). We celebrated the 75th anniversary of that dedication in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duke Gardens is considered Shipman’s greatest work and a national architectural treasure. Most of the approximately 650 other gardens she designed have long since disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="nature" /><category term="garden" /><summary type="html">Source: Duke University Sarah P. Duke Gardens has been serving the Duke and Durham communities for more than 80 years. The idea of a public garden arose in the early 1930s, due to the vision and enthusiasm of Dr. Frederic M. Hanes, an early member of the original faculty of Duke Medical School.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apples</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/plant/nature/2018/08/23/apples.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apples" /><published>2018-08-23T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-23T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/plant/nature/2018/08/23/apples</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/plant/nature/2018/08/23/apples.html">&lt;p&gt;An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple trees are cultivated worldwide, and are the most widely grown species in
the genus Malus. The tree originated in Central Asia, where its wild ancestor,
Malus sieversii, is still found today. Apples have been grown for thousands of
years in Asia and Europe, and were brought to North America by European
colonists.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="plant" /><category term="nature" /><category term="nature" /><summary type="html">An apple is a sweet, edible fruit produced by an apple tree.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Kiwifruit</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/plant/nature/2018/08/22/kiwifruit.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Kiwifruit" /><published>2018-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/plant/nature/2018/08/22/kiwifruit</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/plant/nature/2018/08/22/kiwifruit.html">&lt;p&gt;Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible
berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most common cultivar group of kiwifruit is oval, about the size of a large
hen’s egg (5–8 cm (2.0–3.1 in) in length and 4.5–5.5 cm (1.8–2.2 in) in
diameter). It has a fibrous, dull greenish-brown skin and bright green or
golden flesh with rows of tiny, black, edible seeds. The fruit has a soft
texture, with a sweet and unique flavor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&quot;/2018/08/20/bananas.html&quot;&gt;bananas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="plant" /><category term="nature" /><summary type="html">Kiwifruit (often abbreviated as kiwi), or Chinese gooseberry is the edible berry of several species of woody vines in the genus Actinidia.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Bananas</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/2018/08/20/bananas.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bananas" /><published>2018-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2018-08-20T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/2018/08/20/bananas</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekylltest/2018/08/20/bananas.html">&lt;p&gt;A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds
of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In some countries, bananas used for cooking may be called “plantains”,
distinguishing them from dessert bananas. The fruit is variable in size, color,
and firmness, but is usually elongated and curved, with soft flesh rich in
starch covered with a rind, which may be green, yellow, red, purple, or brown
when ripe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A banana is not commonly used in pizza&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tags: fruits, nature, Nature, plant, and yellow&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tags: Nature fruits nature plant yellow&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Related:&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="plant" /><category term="nature" /><category term="fruits" /><category term="yellow" /><category term="Nature" /><summary type="html">A banana is an edible fruit – botanically a berry – produced by several kinds of large herbaceous flowering plants in the genus Musa.</summary></entry></feed>